<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="/CSS-Advanced-Exam/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/CSS-Advanced-Exam/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-08-11T17:21:42+03:00</updated><id>/CSS-Advanced-Exam/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Best Coin</title><subtitle>Getting better!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Crypto Trader XBTOI Wins Bermuda Crypto License</title><link href="/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/15/trader.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Crypto Trader XBTOI Wins Bermuda Crypto License" /><published>2019-07-15T19:09:21+03:00</published><updated>2019-07-15T19:09:21+03:00</updated><id>/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/15/trader</id><content type="html" xml:base="/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/15/trader.html">&lt;p&gt;Global crypto finance firm XBTO International (XBTOI) has gained legal status in Bermuda. XBTOI acquired a Bermuda Monetary Authority License under the island’s 2018 Digital Asset Business Act according to a statement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moving to Bermuda in April 2018, XBTOI is the third firm to receive a license from the regulator to date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Per its domain, XBTOI operates on multiple finance fronts including over the counter desk trading, consulting, asset management, and VC work. The firm is looking to capitalize on the licensing with new product rollouts concerning digital asset solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Solutions, it said, that were not available in other countries.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Global crypto finance firm XBTO International (XBTOI) has gained legal status in Bermuda. XBTOI acquired a Bermuda Monetary Authority License under the island’s 2018 Digital Asset Business Act according to a statement.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Facebook Libra Might Never Launch, SEC Disclosure</title><link href="/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/14/facebook.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Facebook Libra Might Never Launch, SEC Disclosure" /><published>2019-07-14T19:09:21+03:00</published><updated>2019-07-14T19:09:21+03:00</updated><id>/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/14/facebook</id><content type="html" xml:base="/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/14/facebook.html">&lt;p&gt;Facebook has acknowledged what many have been saying – that regulatory issues may be an insurmountable barrier to the launch of its Libra global cryptocurrency project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a frank disclosure in the firm’s latest quarterly report to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), the firm said that the many barriers it will face regarding regulating a new technology with unclear rules in the U.S. and other nations of the world, mean “there can be no assurance that Libra or our associated products and services will be made available in a timely manner, or at all.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Our participation in the Libra Association will subject us to significant regulatory scrutiny and other risks that could adversely affect our business, reputation, or financial results,” Facebook says.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And not only is Libra “based on relatively new and unproven technology,” the laws and regulations around digital currency are “uncertain and evolving.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Libra has drawn significant scrutiny from governments and regulators in multiple jurisdictions and we expect that scrutiny to continue,” the SEC filing states.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the firm says, the Libra project – which could potentially bring about crypto adoption to the billions of Facebook users – has caused something of an uproar in regulatory circles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Central banks, government ministers and watchdog chiefs have been lining up to demand more information on the project over fears it could pose a threat to central bank money and financial stability, and provide a global avenue for money laundering and fraud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The G7 nations formed a task force to look into issues around cryptocurrencies, but with a steely focus on Libra. It concluded earlier in July that regulations of the “highest standard” would be needed to govern the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some, including the head of the House Financial Services Committee, have even called for the project to be halted while such concerns are addressed.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Facebook has acknowledged what many have been saying – that regulatory issues may be an insurmountable barrier to the launch of its Libra global cryptocurrency project.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Watch the Senate Banking Crypto Regulation Hearing Live</title><link href="/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/13/Senate.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Watch the Senate Banking Crypto Regulation Hearing Live" /><published>2019-07-13T19:09:21+03:00</published><updated>2019-07-13T19:09:21+03:00</updated><id>/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/13/Senate</id><content type="html" xml:base="/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/13/Senate.html">&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs is holding its hearing on regulatory frameworks for cryptocurrencies and blockchain today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The open session, titled “Examining Regulatory Frameworks for Digital Currencies and Blockchain,” is set to start at 10:00 a.m. EST (14:00 UTC). It’s not so far been made clear if the event will be more of a fact-finding mission or if specific legislation will be discussed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Testifying as expert witnesses will be Circle CEO Jeremy Allaire, representing the Blockchain Association; Rebecca Nelson, a member of the Congressional Research Service specializing in international trade and finance; and Mehrsa Baradaran, a law professor at the University of California Irvine School of Law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hearing will be livestreamed and you can watch it here.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The U.S. Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs is holding its hearing on regulatory frameworks for cryptocurrencies and blockchain today.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bitcoin’s Largest Blockchain Just Launched Crypto Exchange</title><link href="/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/12/Man.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bitcoin’s Largest Blockchain Just Launched Crypto Exchange" /><published>2019-07-12T19:09:21+03:00</published><updated>2019-07-12T19:09:21+03:00</updated><id>/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/12/Man</id><content type="html" xml:base="/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/12/Man.html">&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin wallet and blockchain explorer provider Blockchain just launched its first exchange platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blockchain’s head of retail products, TD Ameritrade alum Nicole Sherrod, told CoinDesk the custodial exchange, called The PIT, can connect to non-custodial Blockchain wallets for nearly instant transfers. Registration opens today, with the ability to trade up to 26 assets rolling out over the next two weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sherrod said that with nearly 40 million wallets already created – and an exchange matching-engine set up in London’s Equinix LD4 data center – PIT could be posed to attract more liquidity than competitors.
“That’s what market makers are looking for,” Sherrod said. “They want to co-locate [data center servers] with you, they want to directly connect to your matching engine. It’s the way it’s done on Wall Street.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indeed, Tom Haller, previously the chief software architect for trading systems at the New York Stock Exchange, contributed to the development of PIT’s matching engine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sherrod added the exchange will measure speed in “microseconds,” like traditional asset exchanges. However, an anonymous industry expert was skeptical about whether that theoretical speed with remain constant under real pressures. The source said many infrastructure dependencies are “almost impossible to model out,” so the system will only prove itself when tested by “real-world trading volumes.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Either way, Blockchain is prioritizing diverse token offerings over margin trading options and the bitcoin software update SegWit, both of which are also on the road map.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Beyond the 26 [assets] we already know what our phase two asset listings are going to be, as well as phase three,” Sherrod said, declining to name any assets beyond what the wallet already supports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It remains to be seen how PIT will compete with mainstream exchanges like Binance and Coinbase, which also offer a plethora of crypto assets. Coinbase was also a wallet provider and brokerage, before it became Silicon Valley’s iconic unicorn exchange.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We’re looking to compete on the overall client experience,” Sherrod said, adding that a new customer support team has become the second-largest division of the company as part of a broader shift to exchange services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mainstream exchanges are generally slow to respond to retail users when market activity spikes, so Sherrod argued that beyond speed this is another area where PIT could rival incumbents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only time will tell if the new revenue flows Blockchain users generate through transaction fees will justify this expansion into the heavily saturated exchange space, with fierce competition for market makers and heavily regulatory costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blockchain is applying for new licenses in various jurisdictions, Sherrod said, but failed to specify which ones. In the meantime, the exchange won’t operate in any jurisdiction that requires a license, a spokesperson added.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Bitcoin wallet and blockchain explorer provider Blockchain just launched its first exchange platform.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Samsung Adds Wallet from Blockchain Phone Rival Pundi X</title><link href="/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/11/Phone.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Samsung Adds Wallet from Blockchain Phone Rival Pundi X" /><published>2019-07-11T19:09:21+03:00</published><updated>2019-07-11T19:09:21+03:00</updated><id>/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/11/Phone</id><content type="html" xml:base="/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/11/Phone.html">&lt;p&gt;Rival manufacturers of blockchain smartphones, Samsung and Pundi X, appear to see the benefits of working together on crypto adoption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Announced by Pundi X in a blog post on Monday, the firms have entered a symbiotic relationship regarding their wallet tech, with Pundi X integrating with Samsung’s Blockchain Wallet and making its XWallet available to the Galaxy S10 phone’s blockchain app options.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This presents a unique opportunity to push blockchain technology and blockchain-based digital assets into the mainstream, reaching the millions of Samsung smartphone users around the world,” firm says in the post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pundi X claims the news makes it the first fintech app in the S10’s blockchain ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S10 users adding XWallet to the Samsung Blockchain Wallet will be able to move cryptocurrencies between the two apps. Pundi X suggests that users can use Samsung’s wallet to store cryptos securely, “like a savings account,” and moving them to the XWallet “checking account” for use in payments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pundi X added that, with XWallet recently becoming available via XPOS – the firm’s blockchain point-of-sale device – more payment options will be on offer for S10 users as a result. XWallet is also connected with XPASS, Pundi X’s NFC-enabled crypto payment card product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Samsung launched its S10 flagship phone back in March, revealing a bold blockchain play that saw it offer the crypto wallet alongside decentralized apps (dapps), merchant payments and other features such as blockchain signing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Details of Pundi X’s device were aired at the Mobile World Congress conference in Barcelona in February and a launch is expected later this year. The prototype XPhone is said to be able to make calls over a blockchain.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Rival manufacturers of blockchain smartphones, Samsung and Pundi X, appear to see the benefits of working together on crypto adoption.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Firearm Wins Patent for Integrating Black Box Guns</title><link href="/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/10/Guns.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Firearm Wins Patent for Integrating Black Box Guns" /><published>2019-07-10T19:09:21+03:00</published><updated>2019-07-10T19:09:21+03:00</updated><id>/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/10/Guns</id><content type="html" xml:base="/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/10/Guns.html">&lt;p&gt;Blockchain has made its way to the firearm industry with a patent issuance to Justifire, a Georgia-based gun appliance manufacturer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Described as a ‘black box’ for your gun, the company’s signature device captures visual, audio, and other data for events requiring lethal force. Sensing sudden environmental changes, Justifire records dangerous encounters with the intention of protecting the right to self-defense in both the legal and public sphere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the patent, the 3 inch by 3 inch by 1.5-inch device will incorporate blockchain technology for end-to-end data integrity. Through blockchain, the Justifire attachment will send data to a network of nodes for encryption and storage. The patent hints at possibly tokenizing the data to incentivize node participation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently, the system uses two mounted SD cards to store encrypted data. Inventor and Justifire CEO Jason Palazzolo argues pairing Justifire with blockchain breathes integrity into sticky legal situations:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Justifire uses a combination of autonomous sensors to capture every aspect of any given situation. In case of self-defence, this data can be used to recreate the actions and events leading up to and after discharge of a firearm,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The firm is seeking additional funding to continue development of its product including new tools like ultrasonics, thermal, and laser imaging radar. With the patent, Justifire is pivoting toward blockchain development and implementation.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Blockchain has made its way to the firearm industry with a patent issuance to Justifire, a Georgia-based gun appliance manufacturer.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Coinbase Pro to Enable Tezos Trading Tomorrow</title><link href="/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/09/TezosTrading.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Coinbase Pro to Enable Tezos Trading Tomorrow" /><published>2019-07-09T19:09:21+03:00</published><updated>2019-07-09T19:09:21+03:00</updated><id>/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/09/TezosTrading</id><content type="html" xml:base="/CSS-Advanced-Exam/2019/07/09/TezosTrading.html">&lt;p&gt;Coinbase Pro announced the coming addition of the proof-of-stake and democratically-governed Tezos blockchain to its institutional trading platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tezos (XTZ), a multi-million dollar blockchain that officially launched in September 2018, offers the opportunity for its stakeholders to vote on-chain on proposed upgrades. When Tezos was added to another Coinbase affiliate, Coinbase Custody, in March, the move was contested by those who opposed the extension of voting rights to custodial token holders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is unclear whether Coinbase Pro will offer “self-amending” duties to users of its platform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before trading is activated, Coinbase Pro must build reserves of the coins in trading pairs with BTC and USD. Beginning on Monday, August 5, the firm will accept inbound transfers of XTZ 12 hours in advance of launch, according to a company blog post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Once sufficient supply of XTZ is established on the platform, trading on the XTZ/USD, and XTZ/BTC order books will start in phases, beginning with post-only mode and proceeding to full trading should our metrics for a healthy market be met,” the company states.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Similar to onboarding other digital assets to the trading platform, Coinbase expects to move through four stages before tezos functionality is fully operational.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first is “Transfer-only,” when orderbooks will only support incoming coins. Once a reserve is established, the platform will enter into the minute-long “Post only” phase, where users will be able to post limit orders that will remain unfulfilled. Third is “Limit-only” in which “limit orders will start matching but customers are unable to submit market orders.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After these embryonic stages, full trading will be enabled. Importantly, Tezos will not be available on Coinbase itself. Tezos held a $232 million initial coin offering (ICO) in 2017, one of the largest funding events at the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last month, Coinbase Pro added trading Chainlink, the company expects to roll out additional digital assets.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Coinbase Pro announced the coming addition of the proof-of-stake and democratically-governed Tezos blockchain to its institutional trading platform.</summary></entry></feed>